She was taking Aaru to Anganwadi.  Aru
's father says, come, I will drop you on my scooter.
Reaching Anganwadi, Aru
started playing there and she was enjoying it a lot
because there were a lot of children around.  She becomes even
happier after seeing children.  I was
enjoying it here a
lot and then food was also available here for the
children to eat, so
my Aaru also sat here and started eating.  Then I got
Aaru's weight checked who was acting too much
and what all we get from Anganwadi.
Today we got oil
from Anganwadi.  Gram and pulses are also available.
As and when things come from the government,
we get those things.  Aaru was
enjoying so much that
she was not getting satisfied and I was thinking
when should I go home, when should I go home but she is
not going.  After some time, Aru's
father also came to take it, so I said,
now you take it, and
started showing him all the things that were printed on the wall.  I
told Aru to come tomorrow son, let's go home now, so
I went home.  Come and see, there is
so much tanning on my face and
now I am going to wash my face.  I
use Moringa Detent Face Wash which
removes tanning.  It brightens the face
and gives a lot of glow to the face
and it is also available on Flipkart and Amazon.
What a good result is visible just after washing the face.  If you
also want this product then comment the link